Guide to the Stanford University Objects Collection SC1048
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Objects
  - Sweater, football, turtle neck, tie at neck, red with block S in black, 59x45cm, long sleeves. [name tag for Thomas M. Williams sewn at neck], ARCH-AM-1984-23 (Box 1)
  - Sweater. Long sleeve, red with white "11" on back. 79X61 cm., ARCH-AM-00-139 (Box 1)
  - Sweater, Rally Committee Chairman & Cardinal Society ring, 1943; ARCH-AM-2016-011 (Box 2)
    ARCH-AM-2016-011.13: James Richardson McBrier (1943) Rally Committee Chairman sweater ARCH-AM-2016-011.14: Blossom Parke McBriar (1943) Cardinal Society ring
  - Sweaters and banner, ARCH-AM-1979-03 (Box 1)
  - Sweatshirt with L'il Injun and "Stanford Sierra Camp", circa 1958; ARCH-AM-2003-011 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: Stanford Class of 1970 25 Years Later / Conventus Vicesimus Quintus, 1995-10; ARCH-AM-2006-033 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt (light blue): Stanford Resilience Project, "Stanford, I Screwed Up", 2015; ARCH-AM-2016-003 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt (black): Center for Teaching and Learning "Peer Tutoring CTL", ARCH-AM-2016-002 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: Toyon 2000-2001 with winking pirate face (in reference to Washing Post article on pirating music and software, based in part on activities at Toyon - article included with shirt), ARCH-AM-2006-032 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt "Wecome to Huang! Summer 2010", ARCH-AM-2010-007 (Box 1)
    Maroon t-shirt from move to new building (Huang Center)
  - T-shirt "Yes on O" signed by people who worked on the Stanford campaign for development of Sand Hill Road, November 1997; ARCH-AM-1997-026 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt (grey): SoCo 99; on back: Sophomore College 99 Stanford University Sterling Quad * Stern * Toyon * Wilbur, ARCH-AM-2000-007 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt (red): SoCo 98 Stanford University; on back: Top Ten Reasons to Go to Sophmore College '98, ARCH-AM-2000-006 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt and pom-pom from final 4 games in Cincinnati Ohio (attended by staff person Pat White), ARCH-AM-1997-001 (Box 1)
    97-01.1 t-shirt 97-01.2 pom-pom
  - T-shirt fragments (20): images and text from t-shirts pertaining to Haas events, programs, or public service themes, 1993-98 and undated; these had been framed and displayed., ARCH-AM-2007-027 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt from Multicultural Springfest 2001. White shirt with green & red design using Hoover Tower, seal, the "S" with the tree and text., ARCH-AM-2001-12 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt from Sophomore College. With quote from John Hennessy"...in a bacon and egg breakfast, the chicken is involved but the pig is committed. Be committed.", 2000; ARCH-AM-2000-026 (Box 1)
    2 t-shirts, same color (white)
  - T-shirt from Summer Research College 2003: dark grey with abstract design & src03 on front, ARCH-AM-2003-020 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt from the 2003 Stanford Multicultural Spring Fest, ARCH-AM-2003-008 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt from thinkBIG Conference on International Women's Health and Human Rights, Feb. 2008; ARCH-AM-2008-022 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt, red with white tree and black lettering: ACADEMIC ADVISOR. UNDERGRADUATE ADVISING CENTER STANFORD UNIVERSITY, ARCH-AM-2006-016 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt, red, with definition of OV [Orientation Volunteer]. Stick figure on back with "anatomy of an OV", ARCH-AM-00-029 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt, red: "stanford parents' weekend '99", ARCH-AM-1999-004 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt, red. On front: "Stanford Robber Barrons" (in white) with Robber Barron clutching books and money., undated; ARCH-AM-2015-009 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt, red. On front: Stanford Football Biggest Upset Ever. On back: Stanford - 24 / #1 USC - 23 [in yellow lettering] / - LA Coliseum, October 6, 2007; ARCH-AM-2007-026 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt, Stanford class of 1980, circa 1980; ARCH-AM-2009-027 (Box 1)
    Red t-shirt with design of Quad gate and palm trees and 80 with Hoover Tower in center of zero
  - T-shirt, with with blue & orange decoration and words: Stanford Multicultural Springfest, 2002; ARCH-AM-2002-20 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: "Community Day at Stanford" (no image), ARCH-AM-2002-16 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: "Donnurban Legends 2002-2003" on front and "It happened to my friend's uncle's roommate... I swear" on back. Grey shirt with yellow print., ARCH-AM-2002-36 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: "I went to Hell for the Centennial, and all I got was this lousy T-shirt", ARCH-AM-1992-17 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: black with graphic from Stanford Summer Research College 2001, ARCH-AM-2001-24 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: DONNER POPS Once you pop, you can't stop!, ARCH-AM-2004-012 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: Solar Oscillations Investigation of the Solar & Heliospheric Observatory (Stanford was one of the institutions along with NASA, Lockheed), ARCH-AM-2002-35 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: sophomore colle: Evolve into your future; back side also lists courses, 2008; ARCH-AM-2008-024 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: Stanford University, Arts Intensive Program, ARCH-AM-2014-010 (Box 1)
    Light Blue Shirt Front: "Arts Intensive/Access Your Creativity." Back: "Access Your Creativity/2011 Arts Intensitive Program/A September Studies Program/Stanford University/Acting Intensive: Theatre and Beyond, Into the World of Film/Ballet Intensive: Innovation in Tradition/Conservation Photography/Design Thinking & the Art of of Innovation/Digital Art and Design in Practice/Fiction Writing/Document Filmmaking/Sound Art"
  - T-shirt: Stanford University, Bing Honors College, ARCH-AM-2014-009 (Box 1)
    Red Shirt. Front: "Bing Honors College/A Stanford September Studies Program/2011." Back: "Shared Intellectual Purpose/Independent Scholarship."
  - T-shirt: Stanford University, Multicultural Springfest, 2014; ARCH-AM-2015-001 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: Stanford University, Program in Feminist Studies at Stanford, ARCH-AM-2015-002 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: Stanford University, Sophomore College Program, ARCH-AM-2014-011 (Box 1)
    Yellow shirt Front: "SOCO 2011/Sophomore College/A September Studies Program. Challenge. Question. Inspire." Back: "2011 Sophomore College Stanford University...[several courses listed]"
  - T-shirt: Stanford University, Stanford Design Group, ARCH-AM-2015-003 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: Stanford XXL Athletic Dept. - red letters on grey shirt, ARCH-AM-2007-005 (Box 1)
  - T-shirts, ARCH-AM-2002-01 (Box 1)
    2002-01.1 Gorbachev at Stanford University June 4, 1990 2002-01.2 "I went to hell for the Centennial and all I got was this lousy t-shirt" Stanford Centennial finale weekend performer, 1991 2002-01.3 Stanford Centennial Finale Weekend 1991
  - T-Shirts (2) from men's final 4 basketball championship, 1998; ARCH-AM-1998-003 (Box 1)
    98-03.1 white t-shirt with logos from all 4 teams on back 98-03.2 grey t-shirt with Stanford cardinal final four March 28 & 30, 1998 on front
  - T-shirts (2) Stanford University, Leland Scholars Program, 2012; ARCH-AM-2014-001 (Box 1)
  - T-shirts (5) and Big Game Button., circa 1977-1992; ARCH-AM-2009-004 (Box 1)
    2009-004.1 - T-shirt: 1891-1991 [on back: Celebrating Stanford Women] 2009-004.2 - T-shirt: Stanford History Department [on back: Lenin Cartoon] 2009-004.3 - T-shirt: Centennial Years, 1985-1991 Stanford University 2009-004.4 - T-shirt: 21st Annual Stanford Pow Wow, May 8,9,10, 1992, Honoring the strength and persistence of Native Cultures 2009-004.5 - T-shirt: Gorbachev at Stanford [on sleeve: June 4, 1990] 2009-004.6 - Button: Beat Cal Big Game '77 with image of tree, axe, and bear.
  - T-shirts (7), ARCH-AM-2007-017 (Box 1)
    2007-017.1 Big Dance '00 [on back: The Big Dance Gang-of-13 with names] 2007-017.2 Herstory 2007-017.3 Stanford Axe Committee 2007-017.4 102nd Big Game Countdown / 102 hours of nitrous bliss 2007-017.5 Stanford Axe Committee 1999-2000 (polo shirt style) 2007-017.6 Viennese Ball 2000 (long sleeve) 2007-017.7 Big Dance '99 The Time Warp
  - T-shirts for Larkin staff 2004, 2005, 2006. All say "Not the biggest - just the best"; each has a different "University Registrar's Warning" on the back, ARCH-AM-2007-001 (Box 1)
    2007-001.1 2004 shirt 2007-001.2 2005 shirt 2007-001.3 2006 shirt
  - T-shirts from Stanford Centennial, ARCH-AM-1991-100 (Box 1)
    1991-100.1 White: Centennial years 1985-1991 Stanford University 1991-100.2 White: Stanford Centennial Run Finale Weekend 1991-100.3 White: Alpha Omega Centennial Stanford Sigma Chi 100 Years 1991-100.4 Red: Stanford Centennial Finale Weekend
  - T-shirts from women's basketball, 1997; ARCH-AM-2005-023 (Box 1)
    2005-023.1 NCAA women's final four 1997 2005-023.2 Stanford Women's Basketball PAC-10 Champions 1997 [from SU bookstore]
  - T-shirts of Branner Hall and other SU themes, ARCH-AM-2005-043 (Box 1)
    043.1 Stanford Women's Water Polo 1992 Tournament - white 043.2 CS 001c Introduction to the MacIntosh Fall Quarter 1990 - white 043.3 Stanford Class of '86 - The Best Yet (with list of happenings) - red 043.4 Cardinal Baller ~since 1891~ / farmology 101 - grey 043.5 B SU '92-'93 / Publicly Envied - Fear of a Branner Planet - black 043.6 Stanford Swim Camp - Backstroke Blueprint for Success - white 043.7 Branner Hall Stanford University - green 043.8 BRANNER (1990) - white 043.9 Prof. Jackson's Mau Mau Uprising - burgundy 043.10 To Go or Not to Go (w/ image of The Thinker / Stanford University Admit Weekend 1995 - white 043.11 Branner Excellence (given to 1989-90 staff, note attibutes design to Frank Lobdell) - white 043.12 Stanford National Swim Camp 043.13 Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Culture [Comm on Black Performing Arts] 1999 043.14 The Amy Biehl Foundation. Voice is Power. April 27, 1995 The Great American Music Hall 043.15 Stanford Masters Swimming ca. 1994 043.16 Frosh and Full of Lilfe / branner / ""The Froshmaker"" [1994] 043.17 Gorbachev at Stanford University, June 4, 1990 043.18 Stanford in Ghana March 26-31, 2001, with map on back
  - T-shirts of the gay and lesbian alliance at Stanford, ARCH-AM-2000-016 (Box 1)
    2000-016.1 OUT ON THE FARM, blue with take-off images from Grant's "American Gothic" 2000-016.2 OUT ON THE FARM, red with take-off images from Grant's "American Gothic" 2000-016.3 OUT ON THE FARM, white with line drawing of Segal statue 2000-016.4 gay and lesbian awareness week 1985, grey; image of two women with labris
  - T-shirts, ARCH-AM-2007-006 (Box 1)
    2007-006.1 "I believe - Stanford Football" with longer text on back 2007-006.2 Think Again National Tour [2002] - on back: 20000 miles, 8000 guests, 1600 volunteers, 100 faculty, and 12 cities in 210 days 2007-006.3 Stanford Centennial Finale Weekend 1991
  - T-shirts: Job Fair, 1980, 1981; first Majors Event 1983; SPORTS book, 1982; and 2 unidentified. 1 cap from Big Game, 1986., ARCH-AM-1986-075 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt "For Olympics Against Olympic Homophobia" peach color with black and red lettering., ARCH-AM-1984-17 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt class of '56, 25th reunion. red, white imprint, "XXV reunion" Golden Gate Bridge and Indian, size 39-40, cotton; 71-47cm., ARCH-AM-1984-31 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt "Out on the Farm" black with purple writing and drawing of Gay Liberation: statue on campus., ARCH-AM-1984-15 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt class of '61, 20th reunion; white, red print, size 14, 56x38cm. Multiple choice logo, reverse "'61", ARCH-AM-1984-32 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt; "Stanford 60," white with red letters, "20th reunion." size 10-12;Reverse - Chappie old guys as runners "60", 49x36cm, short sl., ARCH-AM-1984-30 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: "I gave Stanford 42% of my grant, and all I got was this lousy t-shirt!" with drawing of Donald Kennedy in bow of a boat, the "S.S. Excess", ARCH-AM-1998-001 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt silk-screen "Gapoo" design by John Cailleau, 1974; ARCH-AM-1984-11 (Box 1)
  - T-shirt: red polyester/cotton, "french cut" for 10th anniversary, May 1982. Designed by Rhio Hiersch, Eric Ward; printed by "T-party," Redwood City, ARCH-AM-1983-01 (Box 1)
  - T-shirts 1970: "Stanford Sierra Camp" and "Strike", ARCH-AM-2008-011 (Box 1)
    2008-011.1 "Strike" - red print on white shirt with closed fist 2008-011.2 "Stanford Sierra Camp" - red print on white shirt with Indian caricature
  - T-Shirts: Stanford African Student Association (2), Accession ARCH-AM-2018-010 (Box 1)
    2018-010.001: Black shirt with white lettering, front: "I am SASA" with lion; back: "Trivia Afrique" with hands.
    2018.010.002: White shirt with red lettering, front: "It's Not A Country" with Africa shape in solid red; back: "It's A Continent/ Stanford African Students Association" with Africa shape showing individual country outlines.
  - T-shirts and 1 banner all bearing images of John Bravman. The banner was unfurled from the 2nd floor balcony of Mem Aud during Bravman's address to prospective freshman., 2005-04-28; ARCH-AM-2005-021 (Box 1)
    2005-021.1 Light grey t-shirt with 4 images of Bravman on front and "Dukakis" on back 2005-021.2 Dark grey t-shirt posterized image of Bravman on front and "Barbecue" on back 2005-021.3 Large banner with image of Bravman
  - T-shirts and a cap from the NCAA women's regional games in Kansas City 2005, ARCH-AM-2007-014 (Box 1)
    2007-014.1 red t-shirt: 2005 NCAA Division 1 Women's Basketball Stanford Cardinal Kansas City Regional March 27 & 29 2007-014.2 white t-shirt: 2005 NCAA Division 1 Women's Basketball Championship Sweet 16 2007-014.3 white cap with "S" on front and NCAA SWEET 16 on right side
  - Tags with Drue Kataoka image from packaged chocolates handed out at event of Dept. of Communication during commencement 2005. Image is Green West with Hoover Tower behind. (3 copies), ARCH-AM-2005-020 (Box 1)
  - Tangle toy, given away at Physics Library event, 2010; ARCH-AM-2010-011 (Box 1)
    AM 2010-011.1 Red Tangle, when closed reads Physics Library, Varian Building, Stanford University, 1964-2010 AM 2010-011.2 Red/Blue/Clear Tangle, when closed reads Physics Library, Varian Building, Stanford University, 1964-2010
  - Tassel with '91, possibly from graduation cap, ARCH-AM-1999-015 (Box 1)
  - Telegraph key - possibly used by Leland Stanford at Promontory Point, 1869, for gold spike ceremony.2 keys, 1 on wood base, both marked CPRR, ARCH-AM-00-047 (Box 1)
  - Telephone call buzzer from Encina Hall with instruction poster, undated, circa 1920?; ARCH-AM-2009-030 (Box 1)
    2009-030.1 buzzer and push button mounted on plate 2009-030.2 instruction poster (copy)
  - The 111th Opening Convocation fan (5 copies) - includes program on one side and "Hail Stanford Hail" on the other, 2001; ARCH-AM-2001-20 (Box 1)
  - The 112th Opening Convocation fan: mosaic of tree over red S on front, program & "Hail, Stanford, Hail" on reverse, 2002; ARCH-AM-2005-016 (Box 1)
  - The Archivist Code. Framed 53X41 cm., ARCH-AM-00-155 (Box 1)
  - The Koret Prize - Cut glass vase (green tint) presented to Gerhard Casper, 1999; ARCH-AM-2000-031 (Box 1)
  - Buttons (3) created by Friends of Prof. Barclay, ARCH-AM-1986-01 (Box 1)
  - Medallions (3), ARCH-AM-1998-007 (Box 1)
    98-07.1 E.N.S.I.C.A.'s visit to Stanford University, Oct. 17, 1990 98-07.2 Centre des Haute Etudes de l'Armement, Session 1964-65 98-07.3 [prize from English oration contest at Japanese school, 1955]
  - Three-ring binder (blue cloth) with embossed U. seal and "STANFORD" on right vertical edge, ARCH-AM-00-033 (Box 1)
  - Tile in Box. Box 6x8x3, Tile= 6x5x2 cm. From San Gabriel Mission, earthquake of 1812., ARCH-AM-00-244 (Box 1)
  - Tiles from water fountain south of Memorial Church, ARCH-AM-2005-027 (Box 1)
  - Tin box labelled "Stanford University", ARCH-AM-1979-08 (Box 1)
  - Tobacco card (Murad Cigarettes) college series 76-100, ca. 1900. Image is man and woman on horseback in front of giant tree with university seal and Stanford pennant. On reverse is list of colleges., ARCH-AM-2002-07 (Box 1)
  - Tobacco silk with image of a runner wearing Stanford suit and with Stanford seal in upper left corner., circa 1900; ARCH-AM-00-027 (Box 1)
  - Tobacco silks with Stanford images; from Murad cigarettes; ca. 1900, ARCH-AM-2001-03 (Box 1)
    03.1 University seal with "Stanford" below (red silk) 03.2 Football player, with seal in corner (white silk) 03.3 Rower with seal in corner (white silk) 03.4 Baseball player with seal in corner (white silk) 03.5 Track and field athlete with seal in corner (white silk)
  - Tools (3), possibly stone carving tools, found during demolition work at Geology Corner. One has "W. J. Munro" (or W. J. Munrok) on it, ARCH-AM-1996-07 (Box 1)
  - Tools used by engineering student Revoe Briggs, '13, ARCH-AM-1984-20 (Box 1)
  - Toonerville trolley sign, red metal with white painted letters, "To Stanford University" and "Waverley Street" (24 x 22 in.), ARCH-AM-1977-04 (Box 1)
  - Tote bag, Stanford ARTS, circa 2014; ARCH-AM-2015-005 (Box 1)
  - Track meet identification ribbons, 1930; ARCH-AM-2004-027 (Box 1)
    027.1 Field pass for California Freshmen vs. Stanford Freshmen, April 11, 1930 027.2 Field 62 [on button] Track, California vs. Stanford, April 19 1930 Stanford Stadium [on ribbon]
  - Traffic directors arm band (red felt with white lettering), ARCH-AM-1978-02 (Box 1)
  - Train whistle (made of cedar) "The BootToot"produced by The Bootleg.com ("unauthorized authority on Cardinal football"), ARCH-AM-2004-014 (Box 1)
  - Tresidder Union key chains, 1981; ARCH-AM-2009-016 (Box 1)
    Two key chains, plastic tag with "tresidder union" on one side and "the people place" on the other
  - Triangular scarf: "Stanford Council B. S. A. camp staff 1944 Camp Oljato", ARCH-AM-1996-08 (Box 1)
  - Trowel used by Herbert Nash in laying of cornerstone of Thomas Welton Stanford library, ARCH-AM-00-005 (Box 1)
  - Trowel used by Jane and Leland Stanford in laying of cornerstone of LSJU, ARCH-AM-00-004 (Box 1)
  - Trowel used by Jane Stanford in laying of cornerstone of Memorial Church, ARCH-AM-00-002 (Box 1)
  - Trowel used by Leland Stanford in laying of cornerstone of Stanford Museum, ARCH-AM-00-003 (Box 1)
  - Twine stamped "The Stanford Bookstore - Stanford University", ARCH-AM-2006-034 (Box 1)
  - Brushes (2)--pointed oval, no handle with silver backing and University Seal (no German phrase). "W.C.R." etched on edge of each, ARCH-AM-2006-031 (Box 1)
  - Buttons (2) from Green Library Access Services: "Get RESERVES" and "LOAN it", ARCH-AM-2007-028 (Box 1)
  - Buttons (2) from Stanford Computer Forum, circa 1990; ARCH-AM-2007-015 (Box 1)
    2007-015.1 Artificial Intelligence Stanford Computer Forum (drawing of cans labeled "Can 'o' Brains") 2007-015.2 Expert Systems Stanford Computer Forum
  - Buttons (2), "I'm Getting Diverse" (OSA), and "Harvest Oct. 15" (Harvest Fair), 1982; ARCH-AM-1984-19 (Box 1)
  - Fountain pens (2)--Waterman's Ideal and Sheaffer's; latter has Frank E. Buck engraved on it., ARCH-AM-2001-15 (Box 1)
    2001-15.1 Waterman's Ideal fountain pen; 2001-15.2 Sheaffer's fountain pen, engraved
  - Pewter Vases (2), ARCH-AM-1991-090 (Box 1)
  - Two plaques: California Harness Horsemen's Association Hall of Fame - one for Electioneeer and one for Leland Stanford, inducted December 18, 2005., ARCH-AM-2006-026 (Box 1)
    2006-026.1 Electioneer's plaque 2006-026.2 Leland Stanford's plaque
  - Two portraits of John D. McGilvray, ARCH-AM-2004-006 (Box 1)
    AM 2004-006.1 larger portrait - by William Barr of SF AM 2004-006.2 smaller portrait
  - Two red felt squares, with felt fringe, with "STANFORD" in white letters on one; possibly meant to be a pillow cover, ARCH-AM-2001-04 (Box 1)
  - Two tiger balm jars with tigers carved on lids, ARCH-AM-1992-06 (Box 1)
  - Two tobacco tins: Edgeworth extra high grade ready rubbed smoking tobacco, Larus & Bros. Co., ARCH-AM-2004-003 (Box 1)
  - Two top hats belonging to Orrin Dunn, ARCH-AM-1998-008 (Box 1)
    98-008.1 beaver skin top hat, extra high 98-008.2 collapsible top hat, cloth
  - Typewriter in leather case. 39x31x42 case. Old Smith Premier., ARCH-AM-00-190 (Box 1)
  - U.S. Civil War era medical bag of Dr. Edward Charles, 1839-1899, Palo Alto physician and health officer.
    United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865.; Palo Alto (Calif.) -- History.; Medicine -- California
  - U.S. "Centennial" Flag (1876), supposedly flown over the University during the 1891-92 year. Purported to have been given to Thomas Albrecht in honor of serving as Student Body President, ARCH-AM-2006-021 (Box 1)
  - U. S. trade dollar, 1878; ARCH-AM-1992-01 (Box 1)
  - United Stanford Employees buttons (2), 1981; ARCH-AM-2009-018 (Box 1)
    2009-018.1 USE LOCAL 715 VOTE YES MAY 7 2009-018.2 I HAVE VOTED HAVE YOU?
  - University seal (bronze) on wooden shield., ARCH-AM-2006-030 (Box 1)
    Note on back reads "The bronze seal was originally part of the mason work of an idol brat from China and erected in Memorial Court of the University. This idol was destroyed by the great earthquake ot 1906. The wood was taken from the bark [sic ?] of the Memorial Church pews which were wracked by the 'quake. The copper piece for hanging this shield was part of the Memorial Church gutter."
  - Unopened bottle of riesling wine from Warm Springs Vineyard, 1879.[Given in honor of Katherine Jonnie Hanks born in Lucile Packard Children's Hospital 11/10/95], ARCH-AM-1995-35 (Box 1)
  - Various t-shirts and list from "The Stanford T-Shirt Museum" at Branner Hall, March 7, 1985; ARCH-AM-1984-61A (Box 1)
    61A.1 Manzanita Stanford's adult luxury mobile home community 61A.2 EDUCOM Stanford 1983; 61A.3 Out on the Farm gay and lesbian alliance at Stanford; 61A.4 Maderathon 10K - race Stanford; 61A.5 You Can Make a Difference - Entrepreneurs in the Public Interest Feb. 25, 1984 at the GSB 61A.6 Stanford Career Fair
  - Victory ball thrown out to crowd at women's basketball games. "Stanford Basketball 'Chalk Up Another Victory for the Cardinal'", ARCH-AM-1997-027 (Box 1)
  - View of Quad & D.S. Jordan in cap and gown in one frame, Post. '06, ARCH-AM-1995-03 (Box 1)
  - Visor, "class of '76, five year visor" red, white letters. 27cm, adjustable head band., ARCH-AM-1984-33 (Box 1)
  - Walking Cane, knarled wood, metal tip, crooked handle, 74 cm. long; belonged to J.E. McDowell, ARCH-AM-00-096 (Box 1)
  - Walking Cane, wood, knarled, crooked handle with monogram on tip, 74 cm long; belonged to Jud Cary, '03., ARCH-AM-00-097 (Box 1)
  - Walking Cane, wooden, knarled, straight 160x10 cm. diameter with metal tip., ARCH-AM-00-095 (Box 1)
  - Walking canes, ARCH-AM-00-062 (Box 1)
  - Wall Hangings (2), Stanford Indian (13 x 13 inches), painted composite board, ARCH-AM-2014-006 (Box 1)
  - Wall plaque in Russian (collected by the Centennial office from other institutions' anniversary events), ARCH-AM-1991-102 (Box 1)
  - Water bottle "Technical Services: the Next Generation", ARCH-AM-1996-09 (Box 1)
  - Water bottle in dumbbell shape given out at basketball game - "Stanford Athletics Home of Champions" "Fry's Electronics", ARCH-AM-1997-005 (Box 1)
  - Water color, Zoological Lab, by E.H. Mitchell, 24x30 cm. framed under glass-51x46x2 cm. Artist signed 1897., ARCH-AM-00-115 (Box 1)
  - Watercolor by David Starr Jordan: reptile with poem, 3/28/10, framed, 1910; ARCH-AM-1985-06 (Box 1)
  - Wells Fargo safe that once housed the gold spike, ARCH-AM-2009-024 (Box 1)
  - White hard hat and commemorative shovel from the topping out ceremony in Green West, March 27, 1998, ARCH-AM-1998-005 (Box 1)
    98-005.1 hard hat with label; 98-005.2 shovel with metal label
  - White plastic hardhard, with "Team Stanford Mansion" on back and "The Leland Stanford Mansion" with image on front, ARCH-AM-2006-024 (Box 1)
  - Window decals (3) on sheet - University seal, "S" with tree superimposed, "S" with "Cardinal" in script over it [2 sheets], ARCH-AM-2001-25 (Box 1)
  - Wine Bottle, ARCH-AM-00-172 (Box 1)
  - Wine bottle - Stanford Alumni Association 1989 Napa Valley Cabernet Sauvignon. Label uses LSJU monogram from the cover of the SU founding grant., ARCH-AM-2006-013 (Box 1)
  - Wine bottle from Palo Alto vineyard, "Angelica", 1890; ARCH-AM-1995-13 (Box 1)